The complete inside story of the West Memphis Three
Paradise Lost 3: Purgatory is a documentary, crime
film directed by Bruce Sinofsky.
A further investigation into the arrest of three teenagers convicted of killing three young boys in Arkansas who spent
nearly 20 years in prison before being released after new DNA evidence indicated they may be innocent.
Self, played by Jason Baldwin.
Self, played by Damien Echols.
Self, played by Jessie Misskelley Jr..
Self, played by John Mark Byers.
Self, played by Gary Gitchell.
Self, played by Terry Hobbs.
Paradise Lost 3: Purgatory is a 2011 American documentary film directed by Joe Berlinger and Bruce Sinofsky, and sequel to
their films Paradise Lost: The Child Murders at Robin Hood Hills (1996) and Paradise Lost 2: Revelations (2000).
The three films are about West Memphis Three, three teenage boys accused of the May 1993 murders and sexual
mutilation of three prepubescent boys as a part of an alleged satanic ritual in West Memphis, Arkansas.
Purgatory offers an update on the case of the West Memphis Three, who were all recognized guilty of the murders in 1994 but
kept on claiming their innocence since then, before culminating with the trio's attempt at an Alford plea.
The film premiered at the 2011 Toronto International Film Festival on
September 11, 2011, before airing on HBO on January 12, 2012.
It received a nomination for the Academy Award for Best Documentary Feature, as well as Primetime Emmy Award nominations
for Exceptional Merit in Documentary Filmmaking and Outstanding Directing for Nonfiction Programming.
The film explores themes of death row, press conference,
arkansas, lawyer, murder investigation.